Guide to the Donald R. MacQuivey Papers M0834
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Donald R. MacQuivey papers
circa 1930-1990
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
MacQuivey, Donald R.
M0834
118 Linear Feet (98 boxes)
Donald MacQuivey was a telecommunications policy analyst during the Cold War, working for Harvard's Radio Research Lab, the Department of State, and the Stanford Research Institute.
Conditions Governing Access
Open for research. Note that material must be requested at least 36 hours in advance of intended use. Audiovisual materials are not available in original format, and must be reformatted to a digital use copy.
Acquisition Information
This collection was given by the estate of Donald R. MacQuivey to Stanford University, Special Collections in May, 1993. Accession 1993-048.
Scope & Contents
The professional papers of Donald MacQuivey consists primarily of correspondence, memoranda, and reports kept by Macquivey in the course of his work. One of MacQuivey's research interests was the dissemination of current information among colleagues; thus there are numerous article clippings, publications, and bibliographical references pertaining to communications.
Donald R. MacQuivey Papers: Series
Bibliographical References
Conferences & Presentations
Correspondence
Organizations
Projects
Publications
Stanford Research Institute
Stanford University
Telecommunications General
Telecommunications Chronological Files
World War II
Personal Files
Audiovisual Media
Biography
Donald R. MacQuivey (1913-1993) was an engineer and policy analyst in the field of telecommunications. He received several degrees from Stanford University, among them Radio Engineering in 1935, Electrical Engineering in 1939, and an MBA in 1942. During World War II, MacQuivey worked for the Harvard/MIT Radio Research Laboratory under Fred Terman, under whose auspices he traveled to Asia as a Technical Observer in 1944. Following the war, MacQuivey worked for the U.S. Department of State, Telecommunications Division until 1962, at which time he was employed by the Stanford Research Institute. MacQuivey's work largely centered on radio frequency allocation and management, as well as satellite communication and its implementation.
Telecommunication; Radio -- History; Science -- History.; Stanford Research Institute; MacQuivey, Donald R.; Consultative Committee on International Radiotelepathy
- Series 1: Bibliographical References
  - Bibliographical References, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Bibliographical Reference Cards (2 small boxes), 1981 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Glossary, References (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - International Telecommunications Policy Bibliographical References, 1965 (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - Scientific Information Management, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Telecommunications Bibliographical References (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Telecommunications Notes & Bibliography Research, 1958-1964 (Box 20, Folders 2)
  - Telecommunications Notes & Bibliography Research: International Communications Bibliography I & II, 1958-1964 (Box 21, Folders 1)
- Series 2: Conferences, Presentations
  - COMSAT/AT&T Presentation, 1971 (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - General Dynamics/Convair Presentation, 1970 (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - International Symposium on Communications, 3/1972 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - MCI/Lockheed Presentation (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - MCI/Lockheed Report Vol.1-4, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Public Decision-Makers Conference, 1972 (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Urban Technology Conference (Box 52, Folder 11)
- Series 3: Correspondence
  - correspondence re: ARTA, 1936 Seamans' Strike, etc., 1936-1938 (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1962-1967 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Chronological Correspondence, 1967-1969 (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - correspondence, incoming, 1969-1973 (Box 12, Folders 7)
  - correspondence, outgoing, 1970-1973 (Box 12, Folders 6)
  - correspondence, incoming, 1974 (Box 12, Folders 7)
  - correspondence, outgoing, 1974 (Box 12, Folders 8)
  - correspondence, incoming, 1975 (Box 13, Folders 2)
  - correspondence, outgoing, 1975 (Box 13, Folders 1)
  - correspondence, incoming, 1976 (Box 13, Folders 3)
  - correspondence, outgoing, 1976 (Box 13, Folders 4)
  - correspondence, incoming, 1977 (Box 13, Folders 6)
  - correspondence, outgoing, 1977 (Box 13, Folders 5)
  - correspondence, incoming, 1978 (Box 13, Folders 7)
  - correspondence, outgoing, 1978 (Box 13, Folders 8)
  - Office of Telecommunications correspondence, 1972-1979 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Visitors correspondence, 1974-1978 (Box 12, Folders 4)
- Series 4: Organizations
  - CCIR (Consultative Committee on International Radiotelepathy), 1960-1978
    - CCIR, 1960-1964 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - CCIR, 1963-1970 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - CCIR, 1978 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - CCIR Study Group Documents, 1962 (Box 6, Folders 4)
    - CCIR Study Group Documents, 1962-1965 (Box 7, Folders 1)
    - CCIR Study Group Documents, 1963 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - CCIR Study Group Documents, 1963-1969 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - CCIR Study Group I-V Documents, 1963-1966 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - CCIR U.S. Study Group III correspondence, 1969-1971 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - CCIR U.S. Study Group III correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - CCIR Study Group III-VI Documents, 1966-1969 (Box 85, Folder 2)
    - CCIR Study Group IV Documents, 1966-1968 (Box 23, Folders 1)
    - CCIR U.S. Study Group IV-C, 1971 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - CCIR Study Group VI-XIII Documents, 1963-1966 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - CCIR Study Group VI-XIII Documents, 1963-1966 (Box 48, Folder 1)
    - CCIR International, 1969-1970 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - CCIR International Study Group VIII-XIII, 1968 (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - CCIR International Study Group VIII-XIII, 1968 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - CCIR U.S. National Committee Documents, 1964-1966 (Box 11, Folders 1)
    - CCIR U.S. National Committee Documents, 1966-1969 (Box 18, Folders 1)
    - CCIR U.S. National Committee Documents, 1960-1964 (Box 10, Folders 2)
    - CCIR Conference & Committee (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - CCIR Documents, 1963 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - CCIR Documents, 1962 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - CCIR Documents, 1962-1963 (Box 86, Folder 2)
    - CCIR People & Organization, 1960-1966 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - CCIR Plenary Assembly, Etc., 1958-1967 (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - CCIR printout (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - CCIR Survey, 1969 (Box 92, Folder 1)
  - NASA (National Aeronautics and Space Administration), 1960-1976
    - NASA Brochures, 1968 (Box 15, Folders 2)
    - NASA Educational Materials, 1974-1975 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - NASA Grants, Proposals, Correspondence, Reports, 1973-1976 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - NASA Information Transfer Satellite Study, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - NASA Press Releases, 1965-1966 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - NASA Press Releases, 1966-1967 (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - NASA Press Releases, 1967-1970 (Box 16, Folders 1)
    - NASA/Skylab publications (Box 77, Folder 1)
    - Space Communications Background (Box 24, Folders 2)
  - NIH (National Institutes of Health)
    - NIH, 1970-1978 (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - NIH correspondence, memoranda, reports, 1973-1974 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - NIH correspondence, 1972-1976 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - NIH 5 Year Proposal Background (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - NIH Highlights, 1973-1978 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - NIH Opthamology Equipment, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - NIH Proposals (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Other Organizations
    - AEMB (Alliance for Engineering in Medicine & Biology), 1974-1975 (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - AEMB Background (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - AIAA COMSAT Meeting, 1968 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - ARPA correspondence, memoranda, reports, 1973-1978 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - CIEM (Center for Integrated Electronics in Medicine)Proposals, 1974-1977 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - CIEM Proposal & Material, 1973-1976 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Communications Information Coordination Center, 1969-1971 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - FCC, 1961-1968 (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - Heart Lung & Blood Center, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - IEEE Award John G. Linvill, 1974-1976 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - IEM Site Visit (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - IRAC (Interdepartmental Radio Advisory Committee) Documents, 1950-1956 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - IRAC Documents, 1956-1961 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - ISL Brochure, 1973 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - ITU/ESSA, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - ITU Atlantic City, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - ITU World Planning Committee, Mexico City Group Photograph, 1967 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - JSEP, 1972-1975 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - NARBA - Havana Conference, 1947 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - Navy, 1974 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - NSF, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - PHA Roster, 1947 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - UNESCO, United Nations, etc., 1966 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - VA Rehabilitation Engineering, 1977 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - WU Recommendations (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Personnel Contacts
    - Persons & Tools (directories, manuals), 1950-1978 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Persons & Tools (directories, manuals, etc.), 1963-1978 (Box 8, Folders 1)
    - Personnel Rosters (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Personnel Rosters, 1946-1962 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Roster Development (Box 29, Folder 9)
- Series 5: Projects
  - DTM-2 (Project 5400)
    - AT&T Tariffs (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - DTM-2 (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - DTM-2 (Box 85, Folder 1)
    - DTM-2 (Box 91, Folder 2)
    - DTM-2 Ed Post Papers, 1965-1966 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - DTM-2 Ed Post Papers (Box 81, Folder 3)
    - DTM-2 Ed Post Papers (Box 82, Folder 1)
    - DTM-2 Filings (SRI), 1965 (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - DTM Policy Study Draft, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - DTM-2 Proposal, Notes, Correspondence, 1965 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - DTM-2 Proposal, Notes, Correspondence, 1965 (Box 44, Folder 1)
    - DTM-2 Questionaire Responses (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - DTM-2 Report Draft, 1956-1965 (Box 55, Folder 1)
    - DTM-2 Tariffs (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - FCC Land Mobile
    - FCC Land Mobile - 3773; 3551; 4554, 1961-1968 (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - FCC Land Mobile Documents, 1968 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - FCC Land Mobile References G-Z, 1967 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - FCC Land Mobile Reports, 1967 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Other DRM Writing & Projects
    - Articles, "House at 110" Journal, 1942-1945 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - COMPOSER, 1946-1988 (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - DRM-authored publications, reports, essays, 1946-1971 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - DRM-authored publications, reports, essays, 1946-1971 (Box 49, Folder 1)
    - Frequency Assignment Administrative Control Thesis (Master), 1956 (Box 53, Folder 15)
    - Frequency Assignment Administrative Control Thesis Background Binders, 1955-1956 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - IAC Survey, Questionaire (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - ITS/SRI Personnel Study (DRM), 1968-1969 (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Opinion Indicator Notes, 1946-1948 (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - TRIM (Telecommunications Research Information Memorandum), 1971-1972 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - TRIM (Telecommunications Research Information Memorandum), 1972 (Box 52, Folder 14)
    - TRIM (Telecommunications Research Information Memorandum), 1971-1974 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - World Telecommunications Survey, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - World Telecommunications Survey notes & draft, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Misc. Projects
    - Africa Telecommunications (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Alaska, 1973-1974 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - ASCEND Case Study, 1967 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - CURTS Application - Frequency Management (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - Background for International Communications- Office of Telecommunication Management, 1965 (Box 53, Folder 16)
    - Deaf Communication Research (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Deaf Communications, 1974-1975 (Box 87, Folder 4)
    - Demand & Markets (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Demeter (Stanford Case Study), 1968 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Frequency Management (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Future Radio Spectrum Use, 1967-1968 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - FREAVEY, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - General Satcom (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Ground Segment Costs (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Ground Transmission System Costs (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - Guttenberg II (Stanford Case Study), 1972 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Home Communications Project, 1967-1969 (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - IR&D memoranda, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Interarea Coupling, 1973 (Box 87, Folder 3)
    - JSEP (Joint Services Electronics Program), 1975 (Box 87, Folder 2)
    - Loma Prieta, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Micropower, 1972-1975 (Box 87, Folder 1)
    - Multi-Access Systems (Box 53, Folder 12)
    - Operations Research, 1957 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - Operations Research Society (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Orbital Spacing (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Palo Alto Case Study binder, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - Palo Alto C. Services (Stanford Case Study) (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Rockies C. Services (Stanford Case Study) (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - Seamart (Stanford Case Study), 1969 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - System Optimization Papers (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Trends, 1972-1974 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Urban Research & Development (Stanford Case Study), 1970 (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Users of Lab Animals, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Xeledop Applications, 1966 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Computers
      - CAI (Computer Assisted Instruction) (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - CAI Dunn (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - Computer Simulation, 1974 (Box 34, Folder 1)
      - Computers/Terminals (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - Computer Use correspondence, 1973-1977 (Box 12, Folders 2)
      - Kimball-Educational Technology (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - MITRE, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - TELINFO TTY Tapes & Printouts, 1972 (Box 89, Folder 1)
    - Television & Cable
      - CATV, 1972-1974 (Box 29, Folder 4)
      - CATV brochures, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - Continuing Education Television (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - MIT CATV Proposal (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Palo Alto/Stanford Cable CATV, 1980-1985 (Box 82, Folder 2)
      - Palo Alto/Stanford Cable CATV, 1980-1985 (Box 83, Folder 1)
      - Television Factbook Map, 1971 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - Television reports, 1972 (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Larry Liu
    - Larry Liu (research assistant) material: articles, publications, correspondence, 1946-1979 (Box 22, Folders 3)
- Series 6: Publications (Articles, Journals, Memoranda, Reports, etc.)
  - Organizations Publications
    - Velikowski (Box 52, Folder 13)
    - U.S. Government Reports, Hearings re: TAC-Taiwan, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 1)
    - U.S. Government Reports, Hearings, 1964 (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - Telecommunications Reports (Washington D.C.), 1968-1973 (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Telecommunications Journal of Australia, 1971-1972 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - TCC Merger report, 1946 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - "Rads" Articles (radicals?), 1972 (Box 53, Folder 17)
    - PEN (Peninsula Electronics News), 1972 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Mexico, Central & South America UNESCO publications, 1964-1968 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Kuaui, Hawaii Reports, 1970 (Box 53, Folder 19)
    - AT&T Overseas Reports, 1962-1965 (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Bureau of the ITC Radio Lists, 1935-1936 (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Canadian Telephone & Cable Television Journal, 1971-1972 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Communication Satellite Staff Report, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - Cooley Report, 1959 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - Directories of Scientific Institutions, Mexico, Central & South America, 1963-1968 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Educational Broadcasting Review, 1971-1972 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Department of Defense Engineering & Scientific Terms Thesaurus (Box 91, Folder 1)
    - Department of State Biographic Register, 1944-1959 (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Department of State Biographic Register, 1959-1962 (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Department of State Telecommunication News, 1961 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - L'Echo des Recherches, 1971 (Box 72, Folder 2)
    - Galloway Report, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Hewlett Thesis, 1939 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - IEEE Publications, 1968-1982 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Industrial Communications (Weekly Information Service), 1966-1970 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - Japan Telecommunications Review, 1971-1972 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Misc. Publications
    - misc. publications re: communications, engineering, 1975-1982 (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - misc. articles re: environment, economics (Box 53, Folder 18)
    - misc. publications re: international politics, economics (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - misc. memoranda - CCIR, IRAC, etc., 1972-1979 (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - misc. reports - CCIR, USSG, FCC, etc., 1966-1970 (Box 88, Folder 2)
    - misc. publications re: ITU, FCC, Treaties, Everyman, CCIR, 1938-1967 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - misc. articles (Box 12, Folders 5)
    - misc. articles, reports, 1960-1985 (Box 53, Folder 14)
    - misc. articles, 1971 (Box 52, Folder 12)
    - misc. articles, publications, 1957-1971 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - misc. notes & reports (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - misc. publications, 1975 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - misc. publications, 1981 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - misc. publications, 1964-1970 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - misc. publications, 1923-1967 (Box 89, Folder 2)
    - misc. reports (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - misc. reports, 1946-1975 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - misc. reports, 1980-1989 (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - misc. reports, 1976-1978 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - misc. reports, publications, 1967-1974 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - misc. reports, publications, 1948-1968 (Box 59, Folder 15)
    - misc. reports, memoranda, etc. (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - misc. reports, memoranda, photographs (Box 53, Folder 20)
    - News Clippings 1962, Telecommunication Journal 1962 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - Newsclippings, 1962 (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - The International Telecommunication Union 1961, 1962 Newsclips (Box 95, Folder 3)
    - 1962 Newsclips, House Debute - combats, Congressional records, How to handle the... May 1962 National Geographic reprint (Box 95, Folder 4)
    - IGY bulletin Summary of Military Communication 1860-1962 ECT. '73 Newsclips (Box 95, Folder 5)
    - Sunset Magazine, July 1980, World Press review, July 1980 (Box 95, Folder 6)
    - Stanford today 1965. Alumni Almanac 1964, Life Oct. '65, Stanford engineer 1980 Stanford GSB 1979-80 Stanford University Bulletin, Stanford review 1964 (Box 95, Folder 7)
    - Newsclips, brochures 62-69 (Box 95, Folder 8)
    - Newsclips 1971-1980, Spectrum March 1980 (Box 96, Folder 1)
    - Sierra Club Bulletin July/August 1980. Sunset August 1980. Economic regulatory Aspects of liquor licensing (Box 96, Folder 2)
    - News Clips 1962-63 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Newsclips 1964 (Box 96, Folder 4)
    - Newsclips 1964 (Box 96, Folder 5)
    - Newsclips 1964-1965 (Box 97, Folder 1)
    - The Volta Review, Newsclips 1965 (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - baNtu July 1965, Newsclips 1965 (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Avionics, Newsclips 1965 (Box 97, Folder 4)
    - Ghana today. News Clips 1965, 1974 + 1980 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Journalism Quarterly Spring 1965, NAEB Journal July - August 1965 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - NAEB Journal July - August 1964, Journalism Quarterly Spring 1964. Relation of Communication Growth to national Political Systems in the less developed countries, articles, NAEB Journal May - June 1964 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Sex and violence on tv, Hearing before the subcommittee on communications of the committee on interstate and foreign commerce house of representatives (Box 98, Folder 4)
- Series 7: SRI (Stanford Research Institute)
  - SRI General Files
    - Visit Requests (Box 56, Folder 53)
    - SRI Consultancy, Travel, People, 1961 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - SRI Program Development (esp. Africa), 1961 (Box 50, Folder 4)
    - SRI publications re: management & communication skills, 1959-1969 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - SRI publications, reports, presentation materials, etc., 1963-1973 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - SRI Funded Research Descriptions, 1971-1978 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - SRI Purchasing, 1971-1978 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - SRI Transition Planning, 1969 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - SRI Bibliographical References (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - SRI Icon Information Consortium, 1972-1974 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - SRI Teleconferencing Study, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - SRI Seminars, 1975-1976 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - SRI reports, 1962-1964 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - SRI reports (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - SRI reports, 1963-1971 (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - SRI reports & souvenirs, 1968 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - SRI reports, 1965-1969 (Box 90, Folder 1)
  - SRI Desk Files
    - Alternatives (Box 56, Folder 30)
    - ARINC (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - American Communications Association (Box 56, Folder 47)
    - AT&T (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Broadcasters (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Charts (Box 56, Folder 44)
    - Combined Contacts (Box 56, Folder 45)
    - Commercial Telegrapher's Union (Box 56, Folder 48)
    - Communication Workers of America (Box 55, Folder 56)
    - COMSAT (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - correspondence (Box 56, Folder 22)
    - DCA (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Demand (Box 56, Folder 35)
    - Department of Defense (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Department of Justice (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Department of State (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Documentation (Box 56, Folder 34)
    - Draft & Final Reports (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - DTM (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Engineering (Box 56, Folder 31)
    - FAA (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - FCC (Box 56, Folder 17)
    - Finance (Box 56, Folder 33)
    - General & Administrative (Box 56, Folder 28)
    - Hawaii Telephone Co. (Box 56, Folder 19)
    - Industrial Communications Association (Box 56, Folder 49)
    - IGC (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Integration (Box 56, Folder 38)
    - International (Box 56, Folder 39)
    - Kosh-Glassman (Box 56, Folder 21)
    - ITT World Communications Inc. (Box 56, Folder 20)
    - Lipinski 304 (Box 56, Folder 29)
    - Model Study (Box 56, Folder 37)
    - Monthly Reports (Box 56, Folder 23)
    - NASA (Box 56, Folder 18)
    - National High Frequency Radio Communication Plan (Box 56, Folder 40)
    - PAG Meetings (Box 56, Folder 24)
    - Policy (Box 56, Folder 32)
    - Press Wireless, Inc. (Box 56, Folder 25)
    - Program Development Reports (Box 56, Folder 26)
    - Questionaires (Box 56, Folder 41)
    - RCA (Box 56, Folder 27)
    - Report Writing (Box 56, Folder 42)
    - Revenue (Box 56, Folder 43)
    - Tasks 3-4 (Box 56, Folder 36)
    - Tropical R&T (Box 56, Folder 46)
    - U.S.-Liberia Radio Corp. (Box 56, Folder 52)
    - Users (Box 56, Folder 51)
    - Western Union (Box 56, Folder 54)
    - Unsorted SRI Desk Files (publications, drafts, correspondendce, notes re: public safety, resume, joint ventures, etc.), 1966-1969 (Box 17, Folders 1)
- Series 8: Stanford University
  - Directories, Visitors, Staff: IC Lab, EE, etc. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Electrical Engineering 108-109 Class Materials- DRM, 1938 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Electrical Engineering 412 reports, 1972-1977 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Electrical Engineering President's Report Background, 1966-1973 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Engineering Department articles, reports (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - GSB (Graduate School of Business) (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - GSB, 1952-1969 (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - GSB Class Syllabus, Handouts, DRM Notes, 1942 (Box 88, Folder 1)
  - GSB Management Course, 1969-1970 (Box 72, Folder 9)
  - IC Lab Log, 1975-1976 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - SEL (Stanford Electronics Lab) Reports, 1968-1975 (Box 7, Folders 2)
  - SEL Reports, 1963-1969 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - SEL Reports (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - SEL Teleconferencing Report, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Stanford class readings, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Stanford Summer College, 1984 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Stanford syllabi, 1974 (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Series 9: Telecommunications General (Key Documents, etc.)
  - Chronology of Telecommunications Advances (Box 33, Folder 6)